Yifan He

17322822858 | № hd990523@gmail.com | V ShangHai, China

SUMMARY

Experienced in working in a productive team and comfortable in feature design and troubleshooting

Enthusiastic about continuous learning and continuous summarization, actively following and keeping abreast of the latest industry technologies

Customer-focused and committed to delivering high-quality work on time

EDUCATION

Concordia University Montreal, QC September. 2018 - June. 2022

Bachelor of Computer Science

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

ByteTube Inc., Montreal

Software Development Engineer - Intern

Jan. 2023 - Sep. 2023

- Collaborated within a high-performing agile team to develop community web applications, utilizing modern development tools to provide community consumption services
- Designed and built pages using EasyUI+JQuery, and implemented corresponding RESTful interfaces with SpringBoot+MyBatis3+MySQL, facilitating the development of customer orders, querying customer points, and enhancing customer redemption functions to improve the user experience
- Leveraged Dynamic SQL and Lazy Loading mechanisms in Mybatis, enabling SQL statements to be dynamically concatenate based on different conditions and queried on-demand to reduce query complexity and augment query performance
- Employed DES and MD5 encryption method for the encryption and decryption of passwords, reinforcing platform password security
- Optimized resource utilization by adding headline photos and other infrequently changed resources to **Redis**, achieving a 30% increase in the loading speed of the home page
- Scheduled a daily task using Quartz to count merchant sales, with visual feedback through ECHATS, empowering merchants with insightful sales analysis

WicroSoft, ShangHai

Technical Support Engineer - Full Time

Feb. 2024 - Present

- Worked in Microsoft Customer Success Service center and provided advanced technical support for Customizing the Microsoft Dynamics365 CRM, diagnosing and troubleshooting complex issues about CRM and Dataverser to ensure high customer satisfaction.
- Collaborated with cross-functional and cross-region teams to identify and resolve systemic issues, enhancing product stability and performance.
- Assisted in the deployment, configuration, and customization of CRM environments, ensuring seamless integration and minimal disruption to customer operations.
- Managed escalations from Tier 1 support, handling high-priority cases involving custom components and environments integrations with urgency and expertise.
- Participated in continuous improvement initiatives, contributing to the enhancement of support processes and customer service strategies related to CRM customizations and Dataverse.

PROJECTS

Detection And Generation Of Machine Reports

- Designed and implemented an application capable of automating the process of extracting data from industrial machines and generating customized reports
- Utilized Spring Boot+Spring MVC+MyBatis to build the back-end architecture and complete database interactions to efficiently process and manage data from machines
- Developed a responsive front-end interface with **Bootstrap** and **JQuery** to reduce development time
- Created flexible report templates using FreeMarker to automate the generation of accurate machine data reports based on user selections

Video Education Platform

- Participated in the development of an innovative online video education platform, focusing on backend functionalities like teacher management, course content publishing, and file uploading, aimed at enhancing students' online learning experience
- Employed a microservices architecture, utilizing Spring Cloud, Vue CLI, and Ace Admin template for front-end and back-end separation. This approach facilitated service decoupling and dynamic expansion, enhancing system maintainability and scalability
- Integrated and utilized Mybatis Generator and FreeMarker templates for code generation, boosting the development efficiency of repetitive code and interfaces by 50%
- Developed course categorization display and editing features using the **Ztree** plugin, which made the management interface more intuitive and simplified the category management process
- Implemented video and related file uploading features, supporting both local and Alibaba Cloud OSS storage. Incorporated large file uploading, breakpoint resumption, and rapid transmission technologies, improving file transfer and retrieval efficiency by 10%
- Contributed to creating QR codes for third-party interface login and registration, saving user time while enhancing the accessibility of the user platform

SKILLS

Front-end & FrameWorks: **Back-end & FrameWorks:** Other Tools & Services: